A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1987-1991, RG 39 FA1505
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1987-1991, RG 39
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, David (1915-2017)
Rockefeller, Laurance Spelman (1910-2004)
FA1505
234.9 Cubic Feet 597 containers
Arrangement
Original order. Alphabetical, in 40 series, primarily by subject/topic.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research in accordance with the terms of donation from the David Rockefeller Estate, January 2019. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Researchers interested in accessing audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
When requesting to view audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
Scope and Contents
The 1987-1991 General Files chronicle management of the philanthropic affairs of the third generation of the Rockefeller family, primarily David Rockefeller and Laurance S. Rockefeller.
For several decades, the Rockefeller family has been involved in virtually all aspects of modern philanthropy at the local, national, and international levels through their foundation activities, as well as their individual personal giving. Major interests include physical and mental health, conservation, education, international relations, politics, population, religion, social welfare, the visual and performing arts, cultural exchange programs, and economic and social development of underdeveloped regions.
The General Files primarily consist of correspondence, reports, pamphlets, memoranda, charters and certificates of incorporation, minutes and meeting records, documentation of contributions, finance and investment materials, real estate records, news clippings, diaries, notebooks, calendars, and audio tapes.
Related Materials
FA1502 Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1996, Index Cards, RG 3-RG 44.
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1987-1991; 39; 234.9 Cubic Feet 597 containers
  Immediate Source of Acquisition note
  Transferred to the Rockefeller Archive Center June 1995.
  - A, 1987-1991; 1; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
    - A - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture - A-Z (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Agriculture - A-Z (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted - Living Rockefeller family members.
    - Agriculture - American Farmland Trust (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Agriculture - American Farmland Trust - Cousins (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Agriculture - Land Stewardship Project (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Agriculture - Sierra Bianca Associates (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Arts, 1987-1991; 2; 22.5 Cubic Feet 58 letter document boxes and 1 legal document box
    - Arts - A-Z, 1
      - Arts - A-E (Box 3, Folder 1-4)
      - Arts - F-N (Box 4, Folder 1-5)
      - Arts - O-Z (Box 5, Folder 1-4)
      - Arts - A-Z - Cousins (Box 2, Folder 4-14)
      - Aleph Society (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Alliance of New York State Arts Council, Inc. (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - American Council for the Arts (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - American Council for the Arts - Cousins (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - American Federation of Arts (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - American Institute of Architects (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Architectural League of New York (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Australian National Gallery (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Bethesda Academy of Performing Arts (Box 6, Folder 6, Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Bethesda Academy of Performing Arts - Cousins (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Business Committee for the Arts, Inc. (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Century Association (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Century Association - Cousins (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Children's Art Carnival (Box 9, Folder 2-4)
      - Creo Society (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Creo Society - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 8, Folder 4-5)
      - "Crown of the Andes" (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Cultural Arts Council of Houston (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Film and Theater Diplomacy (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Gutman, Judith Mara (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Institute for Art and Urban Resources (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Institute for Contemporary Art, Boston, Massachusetts (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Japan Art Association (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - A-Z (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Lincoln Center Theatre (Box 11, Folder 6, Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Lower Manhattan Cultural Council (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Municipal Art Society (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - National Academy of Design (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - National Committee for the Vatican Judaica Exhibition (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - New York Foundation for the Arts (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - New York Foundation for the Arts - Cousins (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - New York International Festival of the Arts (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Royal Academy Trust (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Studio in a School Association (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Studio in A School Association - Cousins (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - World Monument Fund (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Yaddo (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Dance, 2
      - Dance - A-Z (Box 14, Folder 3-4)
      - Dance - A-Z - Cousins (Box 8, Folder 8-9)
      - Dance Theatre of Harlem (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - National Dance Institute (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - New York City Ballet (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - School of American Ballet, Inc. (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - School of American Ballet, Inc. - Cousins (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Films, 3
      - Films - A-F (Box 15, Folder 5-7)
      - Films - G-R (Box 16, Folder 1-6)
      - Films - S-Z (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
      - Films - A-C - Cousins (Box 8, Folder 12-13)
      - Films - D-R - Cousins (Box 19, Folder 1-7)
      - Films - S-Z - Cousins (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
      - American Soviet Film Initiative (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - American Soviet Film Initiative - Cousins (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Future Wave (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Future Wave - Cousins (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Horizon Communications (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Ideal Communications (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Informed Democracy (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Mediators Foundation, Inc. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Galleries, 4
      - Galleries - A-Z (Box 18, Folder 2-3)
      - Hirschl Adler Galleries (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Katonah Gallery (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Katonah Gallery - Cousins (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Libraries, 5
      - Libraries - A-Z (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
      - Libraries - A-Z - Cousins (Box 23, Folder 2-3)
      - Center for the Study of Presidency (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Center for the Study of the Presidency - Cousins (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - La Casa del Libro (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Library of Congress (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - New York Public Library (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
      - New York Public Library - A-Z (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - New York Public Library - Printed Matter (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - New York Public Library - Cousins (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - The Pierpont Morgan Library (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - The Pierpont Morgan Library - Cousins (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Portland Public Library (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Portland Public Library - Cousins (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Memorials, 6
      - Memorials - A-Z (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Museums, 7
      - Museums - A-B (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Museums - C-M (Box 25, Folder 1-6)
      - Museums - N-R (Box 26, Folder 1-4)
      - Museums - S-Z (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
      - Museums - A-I - Cousins (Box 23, Folder 8-13)
      - Museums - M-Z - Cousins (Box 30, Folder 1-5)
      - Academy of Natural Sciences of Philadelphia (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - American Museum of Natural History (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - American Museum of Natural History - Cousins (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Blerancourt (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Blerancourt - Cousins (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Brattleboro Museum and Art Center (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Brooklyn Children's Museum (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Buffalo Bill Historical Center (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - The Frick Collection (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - The Frick Collection - Cousins (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Wendell Gilley Museum of Bird Carving, Inc. (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Wendell Gilley Museum of Bird Carving - Cousins (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - The Israel Museum (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - The Metropolitan Museum of Art - A-Z (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - The Metropolitan Museum of Art - Contributions (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - The Metropolitan Museum of Art - Cousins (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Mexican Museum (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - Montshire Museum of Science (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Museum of American Folk Art (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Museum of American Indian (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Museum of Broadcasting (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Museum of the City of New York (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Museum of Contemporary Art, Los Angeles, California (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, Massachusetts (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, Massachusetts - Cousins (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Museum of Flight (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Museum of Modern Art (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Museum of Modern Art - A-Z (Box 32, Folder 3-4)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Contributions (Box 32, Folder 5, Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Contributions - Cousins (Box 30, Folder 12, Box 202, Folder 4)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Finances, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Finances - Investment Committee, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Meetings (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Museum President's Conference, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Museum President's Conference, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Printed Matter (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Museum of Television and Radio (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - National Building Museum (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - New Britain Museum of American Art (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Rodin Museum (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - San Antonio Museum of Art (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Smithsonian Institution (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Smithsonian Institution - Cousins (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - Smithsonian Institution - National Gallery of Art (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Smithsonian Institution - National Gallery of Art - Cousins (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - Smithsonian Institution - National Museum of American Art (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - South Street Seaport Museum (Box 36, Folder 2-3)
      - United States Holocaust Memorial (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Whitney Museum of American Art (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Whitney Museum of American Art - Cousins (Box 30, Folder 15)
      - Wildlife of the American West Museum (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Winterthur Museum and Gardens (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Music, 8
      - Music - A (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Music - B-M (Box 38, Folder 1-5)
      - Music - N-Z (Box 39, Folder 1-2)
      - Music - A-M - Cousins (Box 30, Folder 16-21)
      - Music - N-Z - Cousins (Box 45, Folder 1-2)
      - Bar Harbor Festival (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Bar Harbor Festival - Cousins (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Boston Symphony Orchestra (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Boston Symphony Orchestra - Cousins (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Brooklyn Academy of Music (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Brooklyn Academy of Music - Cousins (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - Cantata Singers (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Cantata Singers - Cousins (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Caramoor Center for Music and the Arts, Inc. (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Carnegie Hall Society (Box 40, Folder 5, Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Carnegie Hall Society - Cousins (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Grand Teton Music Festival (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Metropolitan Opera Association (Box 41, Folder 3, Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Philharmonic Symphony Society of New York (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Paintings, 9
      - Paintings - A-Z (Box 42, Folder 3-4)
    - Poetry, 10
      - Poetry - A-Z (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Publications, 11
      - Publications - A-E (Box 43, Folder 2-6)
      - Publications - H-Q (Box 44, Folder 1-6)
      - Publications - R-Z (Box 46, Folder 1-2)
      - Publications - A-S - Cousins (Box 45, Folder 8-16)
      - Publications - T-Z - Cousins (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - Bantam Books (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Brembeck, Howard S. (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Center for Investigative Reporting (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Center for War/Peace Studies (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Chief Executive (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Data Center (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Element Books, LTD (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Reader's Digest (Box 48, Folder 4-5)
      - Reader's Digest - A-Z (Box 49, Folder 1-5)
      - Reader's Digest - Annual Report (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Reader's Digest - Board of Directors (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Reader's Digest - Board of Directors - Rockefeller, Laurance S. (Box 50, Folder 3-4)
      - Reader's Digest - Finances (Box 50, Folder 5, Box 51, Folder 1)
      - Reader's Digest Association - Meetings (Box 51, Folder 2-4)
      - Reader's Digest - Printed Matter (Box 52, Folder 1-3)
      - Small Press Center (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Times Mirror (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - Ack. of Books - A-Z (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Restorations, 12
      - Restorations - A-B (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - Restorations - C-Z (Box 54, Folder 1-7)
      - Restorations - A-Z - Cousins (Box 47, Folder 4-6)
      - The Casements (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - Foundation for the New Haven Green, Inc. (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Fraunces Tavern and Museum, New York, NY (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - Hudson River Sloop Clearwater (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - Middleton Place and Foundation (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - Mount Vernon Ladies' Association (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - New York Landmarks Conservancy (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - Preservation League of New York State (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Save Venice, Inc. (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Statue of Liberty - Ellis Island Foundation (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Statue of Liberty - Ellis Island Foundation - Cousins (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - Versailles Foundation (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Versailles Foundation - Cousins (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Sculpture, 13
      - Sculpture - A-Z (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Theatre, 14
      - Theatre - A-Z (Box 57, Folder 1-6)
      - Theatre - A-Z - Cousins (Box 58, Folder 4-9)
      - Mirror Theatre (Mirror Repertory Company) (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - Mirror Theatre - Finances, 1984-1986 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - The Mirror Theatre - Cousins (Box 58, Folder 10)
      - New York Shakespeare Festival (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - New York Shakespeare Festival - Cousins (Box 58, Folder 11)
      - Shakespeare Globe Theatre (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - Theatre Development Fund (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Aviation, 1987-1991; 3; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
    - Aviation - A-Z (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Eastern Air Lines (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Eastern Air Lines - Board of Directors - Rockefeller, Laurance S. (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Eastern Air Lines - Meetings (Box 60, Folder 4, Box 61, Folder 1-2)
    - Eastern Air Lines - Printed Material (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Eastern Air Lines - Texas Air, 1988 August 8 (Box 61, Folder 4-5)
    - Executive Air Fleet (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Flight Safety Foundation (Box 62, Folder 2-3)
  - B-C, 1987-1991; 4; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
    - B - Miscellaneous (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - C - Miscellaneous (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Civic, 1987-1991; 5; 9.11 Cubic Feet 24 letter document boxes
    - Civic - A-Z, 1
      - Civic - A-M (Box 63, Folder 2-6)
      - Civic - N-Z (Box 64, Folder 1-4)
      - Civic - A-M - Cousins (Box 66, Folder 1-5)
      - Civic - N-Z - Cousins (Box 67, Folder 1-4)
      - American Citizenship Education Project (Box 67, Folder 5-6)
      - American Civil Liberties Union Foundation (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - American Civil Liberties Union Foundation - Contributions (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - American Civil Liberties Union Foundation - Cousins (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Center for Constitutional Rights (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - Center for Responsive Politics (Box 68, Folder 3-4)
      - Citizen Action (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - Citizen's Leadership Foundation (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - Citizen's Participation Project (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - Community Council of Greater New York (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - Council on Municipal Performance (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - France America Liberty Fund (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - Inform, Inc. (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - Inform, Inc. (Box 69, Folder 4-5)
      - League of Women Voters (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - League of Women Voters Education Fund (Box 70, Folder 1-2)
      - National Center for Policy Alternatives (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - National Executive Service Corps (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - National Executive Service Corps - Cousins (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - National Training and Information Center (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - National Urban Coalition (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Nautilus Pacific Action Research (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - Partners for Livable Places (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - Partners for Livable Places - Cousins (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - People for the American Way (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - People for the American Way - Cousins (Box 73, Folder 1-2, Box 74, Box 75, Folder 1)
      - Public Voice for Food and Health Policy (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - Starserve (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - Tennessee Valley Authority Board Appointment Coalition (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - Texans United Education Fund (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - Volunteer (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - Western Organization of Resource Councils (Box 76, Folder 3)
      - The Williamsburg Charter Foundation (Box 76, Folder 4)
      - Chambers of Commerce - A-Z (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - New York City, 2
      - New York City - A-B (Box 76, Folder 6)
      - New York City - C-Z (Box 77, Folder 1-4)
      - New York City - F-Z - Cousins (Box 80, Folder 1-2)
      - Bronx 2000 (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - Bronx 2000 - Cousins (Box 80, Folder 3)
      - Bronx Frontier Development Corporation - Cousins (Box 80, Folder 4)
      - Citizens Committee for New York City (Box 78, Folder 2-3)
      - Citizen's Committee for New York City - Cousins (Box 80, Folder 5)
      - Citizens Housing and Planning Council of New York (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - Community Preservation Corporation (Box 79, Folder 1)
      - New York Board of Trade, Inc. (Box 79, Folder 2)
      - New York Chamber of Commerce and Industry (Box 79, Folder 3)
      - New York City (Box 79, Folder 4)
      - New York City Housing Partnership (Box 79, Folder 5)
      - New York City Partnership - A-Z (Box 81, Folder 1-4)
      - New York City Partnership - Board of Directors (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - New York City Partnership - Contributions (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - New York City Partnership - Meetings-Board Meeting, 1987 June 15 (Box 82, Folder 3-4)
      - New York City Partnership - Printed Matter (Box 82, Folder 5)
      - NonProfit Coordinating Committee of New York (Box 82, Folder 6)
      - Regional Plan Association (Box 83, Folder 1)
      - Regional Plan Association - Cousins (Box 80, Folder 6)
      - New York City Police Foundation, Inc. (Box 83, Folder 2)
      - Volunteer Consulting Group, Inc. (Box 83, Folder 3)
      - Volunteer Consulting Group, Inc. - Cousins (Box 80, Folder 7)
      - Washington Heights and Inwood Development Corporation (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - New York State, 3
      - New York State - A-Z (Box 83, Folder 5-6)
      - New York State - A-Z - Cousins (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - United States Government, 4
      - United States Government (USG) - A-Z (Box 84, Folder 1)
      - United States Government (USG) - A-Z (Box 86, Folder 1)
      - American Agenda (Box 84, Folder 2)
      - Government Accountability Project (Box 80, Folder 9-10, Box 85, Folder 1-2)
      - White House Endowment Fund (Box 84, Folder 3)
      - Bicentennial - A-Z (Box 84, Folder 4)
      - Bicentennial - A-Z - Cousins (Box 85, Folder 4)
      - United States Association of Former Members of Congress - Cousins (Box 85, Folder 3)
      - National Commission on Children (Box 86, Folder 2)
      - United States Information Agency (Box 86, Folder 3)
      - United States Information Agency - Cousins (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Clubs, 1987-1991; 6; 1.9 Cubic Feet 5 letter document boxes
    - Clubs - A-F (Box 86, Folder 4-5)
    - Clubs - G-Z (Box 87, Folder 1-4)
    - Clubs - C-F - Cousins (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Bohemian Grove/Club (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Cosmos Club (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Knickerbocker Club (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - New York Yacht Club (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - The River Club (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - University Club (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - The Wings Club (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Woodstock Golf and Tennis Club (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, 1987-1991; 7; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
    - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, 1987-1991 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation - A-Z (Box 89, Folder 4-5)
    - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation - A-M - Cousins (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation - Printed Matter (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation - Annual Report (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation - Raleigh Tavern Society (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Folk Art Center (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Commercial Venture, 1987-1991; 8; 3.42 Cubic Feet 9 letter document boxes
    - Commercial Venture - A-E (Box 91, Folder 1-4)
    - Commercial Venture - E-M (Box 92, Folder 1-5)
    - Commercial Venture - M-T (Box 93, Folder 1-6)
    - Commercial Venture - U-Z (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Commercial Venture - H-L - Cousins (Box 101, Folder 1-2)
    - Breul & Unger Associates, Inc. (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - International Process Systems, Inc. (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Lone Wolf Systems, Inc. (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Mindcenter Corporation (Box 95, Folder 1-2)
    - Oblensky, Alexis Guy (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Rogue Valley Water (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Slaughter Enterprises, Inc. (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Banking - A-Z (Box 96, Folder 2-3)
    - Banking - Banca Nazionale del Lavore (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - A-B (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - C-M (Box 97, Folder 1-4)
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - Global Investment Forum (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - International Advisory Committee (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Banking - Chase Manhattan Bank - N-Z (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Insurance - A-Z (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Conservation, 1987-1991; 9; 17.85 Cubic Feet 47 letter document boxes
    - Conservation - A-Z, 1
      - Conservation - A-B (Box 98, Folder 5)
      - Conservation - C-J (Box 99, Folder 1-4)